Guide to the Katherine S. Dreier Papers / Societe Anonyme Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Katherine S. Dreier: Correspondence, 1906-1952; Series I; 16; (41 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - "M" general, 1917-50, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 655-657)
    - M. Grumbacher Inc., 1935-36 (Box 23, Folder 658)
    - Maas, Marie Menken, 1944-45 (Box 23, Folder 659)
    - Macbeth, William, 1913, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 660)
    - McBride, Henry, 1921-50, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 661)
      See also: Creative Art, box 9, folder 265
    - McCall's Magazine, 1921, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 662)
    - McCrudden, Francis Lambert, 1948-49 (Box 23, Folder 663)
    - MacDonald, Thoreau, 1927 Nov 25 (Box 23, Folder 664)
    - Macgowan, Kenneth, 1921 Mar 18 (Box 23, Folder 665)
    - McKibbin, David Milton Kendall, 1951-52 (Box 23, Folder 666)
    - McLouth, Mildred
      See: Los Angeles County Museum, box 22, folder 644
      See: Seattle Fine Arts Society, box 31, folder 930
    - MacMaster, Amy K., 1923 (Box 23, Folder 667)
    - MacMorris, Daniel, 1938, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 668)
    - Magazine of Art (New York, N.Y.), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 669)
    - Magnin, Fannie, 1948-51, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 670)
    - Malinovsky, Constantino, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 671)
    - Mallett, Daniel Trowbridge, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 672)
    - Manes, Alfred, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 673)
    - Marc, Maria, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 674)
    - Marcoussis, Louis, 1927, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 675)
    - Margaret Brown Gallery, 1949-50 (Box 23, Folder 676)
    - Marie Harriman Gallery, 1932, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 677)
    - Marin, John, 1921-49 (Box 23, Folder 678)
    - Marsh, Fred Dana, 1924 Jan 17 (Box 23, Folder 679)
    - Maryland Institute, College of Art, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 680)
    - Mataré, Ewald, 1949, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 681)
    - Matta Echaurren, Roberto Sebastián, 1941-49, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 682)
    - Mattatuck Historical Society, 1947-52, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 683)
    - Matulka, Jan, 1920-49 (Box 23, Folder 684)
    - Matulka, Lida
    - Mayor Gallery, 1933 (Box 23, Folder 685)
    - Meene, B. G., 1918, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 686)
    - Mehrgut, Gertrud, 1948-49 (Box 23, Folder 687)
    - Meier, Norman Charles, 1935-37 (Box 23, Folder 688)
    - Melvin, A. Gordon, 1934 Nov 19 (Box 23, Folder 689)
    - Mermet, Irene, 1924-25, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 690)
    - Merz, Max, 1925-26 (Box 24, Folder 691)
      See also: Elizabeth Duncan-Schule, box 13, folder 343
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.), 1921-41 (Box 24, Folder 692)
    - Meyer-Gerhard, Anton, 1921-33 (Box 24, Folder 693)
    - Milwaukee Art Institute, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 694)
    - Miniature Photo Laboratories Co., 1936 (Box 24, Folder 695)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1921, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 696)
    - Minnesota Historical Society, 1941-42 (Box 24, Folder 697)
    - Miro, Joan, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 698)
    - Moffat, Abbot Loc (Box 24, Folder 699)
    - Moholy-Nagy, László, 1923-44, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 700)
    - Moholy-Nagy, Lucia, 1926, 1928, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 701)
    - Moholy-Nagy, Sibyl, 1938, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 702)
      See also: László Moholy-Nagy, box 24, folder 700
    - Moll, Ewald, 1931, 1934, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 703)
    - Moll, Leo Ziemssen, 1931-34, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 704-705)
    - Mollenhauer, Ernst, 1923, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 706)
    - Molzahn, Johannes, 1926-50, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 707-709)
    - Molzahn, Loretta
      See also: Kahin, Carmody, Schramm & Kellogg, box 19, folder 558
      See also: Pond-Ekberg Company, box 29, folders 846-848
    - Mondrian, Piet, 1926-42, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 710)
    - Montgomery Museum of Fine Arts, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 711)
    - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1926, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 712)
    - Montross Gallery, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 713)
    - Mooney Molders Defense Committee, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 714)
    - Moor, Arthur Prichard, 1930-51, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 715-716)
    - Moore, Marianne
      See: Dial, box 10, folder 297
    - Morgan, Anne Tracy, 1921-48 (Box 25, Folder 717)
    - Morgan, Ruth, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 718)
    - Morton, Dudley J., 1950 Sep 5 (Box 25, Folder 719)
    - Morton, Rosalie Slaughter, 1924-27 (Box 25, Folder 720)
    - Mount Vernon Seminary, 1925-26 (Box 25, Folder 721)
    - Mueller-Munk, Peter, 1927-28, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 722)
    - Müller & I. Kiepenheuer G. M. B. H. Verlag, 1934, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 723)
    - Mumaw, Barton, 1939-47, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 724)
    - Mumford, Lewis
      See: Pierre Loving (1929 Nov 29), box 22, folder 645
    - Munnich, Arnold, 1920 (Box 25, Folder 725)
    - Münter, Gabriele, 1925-27, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 726)
    - Murray, George, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 727)
      See also: Peggy Murray, box 25, folder 728
    - Murray, Peggy, 1939-46, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 728)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1924-43 (Box 25, Folder 729)
      See also: Oversize, box 130, folder 2874
    - Museum of Fine Arts (Springfield, Mass.), 1935-41, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 730-731)
    - Museum of French Art (New York, N.Y.), 1920 Jan 10 (Box 25, Folder 732)
    - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), 1929-51, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 733-738)
      See also: Henry R. Hope, box 18, folder 503
    - Museum of the City of New York, 1926 Jan 29 (Box 26, Folder 739)
    - Myers, Roland M., 1940, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 740)
    - "N" general, 1921-51, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 741)
    - Narodny, Ivan, 1926-33 (Box 26, Folder 742)
    - Nation, 1921-31, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 743)
      See also: Oswald Garrison Villard, box 35, folders 1046-1047
    - National Arts Club (New York, N.Y.), 1926 Dec 6 (Box 26, Folder 744)
    - National Association for American Composers and Conductors, 1934 Apr 22 (Box 26, Folder 745)
    - National Broadcasting Company, Inc., 1926-30, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 746)
      See also: Box 47, folder 1379
    - National City Bank of New York, 1924 Dec 10 (Box 26, Folder 747)
    - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship (U.S.), 1944 Jan 26 (Box 26, Folder 748)
    - National Gallery of Canada, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 749)
    - Nationalmuseum (Sweden), 1936 (Box 26, Folder 750)
    - Nau, Armand, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 751)
    - Nearing, Scott
      See: World Events, box 38, folder 1121
    - Neresheimer, Lore, 1933-34 (Box 26, Folder 752)
    - Netherland-America Foundation, 1937 Oct 15 (Box 26, Folder 753)
    - Netherlands Information Bureau (New York, N.Y.), 1949 May 19 (Box 26, Folder 754)
    - Neue Kunst Fides, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 755)
    - Neumann, J. B., 1923-50, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 756)
    - New Gallery (New York, N.Y.), 1927 (Box 26, Folder 757)
    - New Haven Lawn Club Association, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 758)
    - New Haven Paint and Clay Club, 1922 Jan 20 (Box 26, Folder 759)
    - New Haven Register, 1942, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 760)
    - New Music Society of California, 1926-27 (Box 26, Folder 761)
    - New Republic (New York, N.Y.), 1919 Jul 19 (Box 26, Folder 762)
    - New School for Social Research (New York, N.Y.), 1930-37, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 763-764)
    - New York Art Calendar, 1930-36 (Box 27, Folder 765)
    - New York Arts Council of the Art Center
      See: Arts Council of the City of New York, box 3, folders 78-81
    - New York Community Trust, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 766)
    - New York Evening Graphic, 1925 Nov 17 (Box 27, Folder 767)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1935, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 768)
    - New York Public Library, 1926-38 (Box 27, Folder 769)
    - New York Regional Art Council
    - New York Society of Women Artists, 1926 Mar 16 (Box 27, Folder 770)
    - New York State Woman Suffrage Party, 1917 Oct 15 (Box 27, Folder 771)
    - New York Times, 1931-42 (Box 27, Folder 772)
    - New York University. Institute of Fine Arts, 1947 Dec 10 (Box 27, Folder 773)
    - New York World-Telegram, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 774)
    - New Yorker, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 775)
    - New-Yorker Staats-Zeitung, 1923 Mar 8 (Box 27, Folder 776)
    - Newark Museum Association, 1923-39, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 777)
    - Newby, Ruby Warren, 1934-42, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 778-779)
    - Newcomb, Florence A., 1926-34, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 780-781)
    - Newton, Edith, 1938 Apr 19 (Box 27, Folder 782)
    - Nicholas Roerich Museum (New York, N.Y.), 1930, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 783)
    - Nichols, Rose Standish, 1927 Oct 9 (Box 27, Folder 784)
    - Niedecken-Gebhard, Hanns, 1931-48 (Box 27, Folder 785-787)
    - Nierendorf, Karl, 1922-42, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 788)
    - Nirenstein, Otto
      See: Otto Kallir, box 19, folder 562
    - Nitzschke, Hans, 1926 Jun 12 (Box 27, Folder 789)
    - Noland, Clara Hampton, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 790)
    - Nordland, Gerald, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 791)
    - Norman, Dorothy, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 792)
    - Norrie, Margaret
      See: Box 85, folder 2173
    - Nura, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 793)
    - "O" general, 1931-51, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 794)
    - O'Connor, Evelyn, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 795)
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1927, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 796)
      See also: Alfred Stieglitz (1931 Feb 14), box 33, folder 971
    - Oley, Martha E., 1926-50 (Box 28, Folder 797)
    - O'Reilly's Plaza Art Galleries, 1947-48 (Box 28, Folder 798)
    - Osgood, Cornelius, 1942, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 799)
    - Österblom, Olof, 1926-27 (Box 28, Folder 800)
    - Outerbridge, Paul, 1924-35, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 801)
    - Ozenfant, Amédée, 1938-39 (Box 28, Folder 802)
    - Ozenfant, Marthe
    - "P" general, 1920-51, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 803-804)
    - P. F. Collier & Son Corporation, 1951 Jan 17 (Box 28, Folder 805)
    - Pach, Walter, 1920-49 (Box 28, Folder 806)
    - Palmer-Sikelianos, Eva, 1939-50, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 807-808)
    - Pan American Association of Composers, Inc., 1931 Mar 1 (Box 28, Folder 809)
    - Panhellenic, 1933-34 (Box 28, Folder 810)
    - Pannaggi, Ivo, 1926-51, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 811-812)
    - Pannaggi, Alice
    - Pattison, Frederick W., 1949-51 (Box 28, Folder 813)
    - Peabody, George Foster, 1920, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 814)
    - Peabody Museum of Natural History, 1942 Feb 19 (Box 28, Folder 815)
    - Pearson, Ralph M., n.d. (Box 28, Folder 816)
    - Pellew, Anna C., 1921 (Box 28, Folder 817)
    - Penguins, 1925, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 818)
    - Penny, Henry B., 1917-40 (Box 28, Folder 819)
    - People's Institute (New York, N.Y.), 1920 Nov 24 (Box 28, Folder 820)
    - Pequeno, Pedro P., 1933, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 821)
    - Peri, Laszlo, 1930 Jun 12 (Box 28, Folder 822)
    - Perls Galleries, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 823)
    - Peter A. Juley & Son, 1926, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 824)
    - Pevsner, Antoine, 1934, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 825)
    - Pevsner, Nathaniel, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 826)
    - Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 827)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 828)
    - Phillips, Duncan, 1943-51 (Box 28, Folder 829)
    - Phillips, Holmead, 1936-49, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 830)
    - Phillips, John Marshall
      See: Yale University Art Gallery, box 39, folders 1125-1137
      See: Yale University Art Gallery Associates, box 40, folder 1138
    - Phillips, Marjorie, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 831)
    - Phillips Memorial Gallery
      See: Duncan Phillips, box 28, folder 829
    - Philosophical Library Publishers, 1948-50 (Box 28, Folder 832)
    - Phocas, Suzanne, 1926-27, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 833)
    - Picabia, Francis (Mrs.), 1920 (Box 29, Folder 834)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 1926 Apr 5 (Box 29, Folder 835)
      From KSD.
    - Pictures on Exhibit, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 836)
    - Pierre Matisse Gallery (New York, N.Y.), 1935 (Box 29, Folder 837)
    - Pinacotheca, 1942-52, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 838-840)
    - Pinchot, Cornelia Bryce, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 841)
    - Pingree, Maxine, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 842)
    - Placht, Karl
      See: Beacon Book Shop, box 5, folder 112
      See: Box 85, folder 2185
    - Plimpton Press, 1923-24 (Box 29, Folder 843)
    - Poets' Theatre, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 844)
    - Pond, Cordelia Sargent, 1945-51, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 845)
      See also: George Walter Vincent Smith Art Museum, box 15, folders 399-401
    - Pond, John D.
      See: Cordelia Sargent Pond, box 29, folder 845
      See: Pond-Ekberg Company, box 29, folders 846-848
    - Pond-Ekberg Company, 1937-51, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 846-848)
    - Portland Art Association, Portland (Or.), 1936 Sep 22 (Box 29, Folder 849)
    - Post, Elisabeth, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 850)
    - Post, Hermann, 1920-39, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 851-852)
      See also: Anna Gaiss, box 14, folder 381
      See also: Heinrich P. Jordan, box 19, folder 552
      See also: Elisabeth Post, box 29, folder 850
    - Potamkin, Harry Alan, 1931 Mar 23 (Box 29, Folder 853)
    - Pougny, Jean (Mrs.), 1926 Mar 5 (Box 29, Folder 854)
    - Prampolini, Enrico, 1923, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 855)
    - Pratt, George Dupont (Mr. & Mrs.), n.d. (Box 29, Folder 856)
    - Price, Lucien, 1937 Feb 3 (Box 29, Folder 857)
    - Puma, Fernando, 1943-45, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 858)
    - Putnam, Wallace, 1926-49, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 859)
    - "Q" general, 1923-48 (Box 29, Folder 860)
    - Quinn, Mary
      See: Mary Sullivan, box 34, folder 981
    - "R" general, 1911-50, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 861-862)
    - R. Piper & Co., 1912 Oct 1 (Box 30, Folder 863)
    - Radcliffe College. Women's Archives, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 864)
    - Radwany, Emery L., 1949-50, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 865)
    - Radwany, Helen
    - Rand School of Social Science, 1930-31 (Box 30, Folder 866)
    - Rasch, Lena Maria, 1920, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 867)
    - Ray, Man, 1920-51, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 868)
    - Raymond, Antonin, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 869)
    - Read, Helen Appleton, 1926, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 870)
    - Rebay, Hilla
      See: Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, box 33, folders 956-957
    - Redfield-Kendrick-Odell Co., Inc., 1924 Jan 3 (Box 30, Folder 871)
    - Rees, Adya van, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 872)
    - Rees, Katherine C., 1923 (Box 30, Folder 873)
    - Reinhardt Galleries (New York, N.Y.), 1926 (Box 30, Folder 874)
    - Rhode Island School of Design. Museum of Art, 1943-50 (Box 30, Folder 875)
    - Richard G. Badger (Firm), 1929 Apr 27 (Box 30, Folder 876)
    - Richter, Hans, 1948-51, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 877)
    - Ridgefield Press (Ridgefield, Conn.), 1934 Aug 13 (Box 30, Folder 878)
    - Riefstahl, R. Meyer, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 879)
    - Robot Engineering Corporation, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 880)
    - Roché, Henri Pierre, 1918-51, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 881)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A.
      See: Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), box 26, folders 733-738
      See: Box 85, folder 2191
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 882)
    - Rohner, Gehrig & Co., Inc., 1932-38, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 883)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1930, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 884)
    - Rose Fried Gallery
    - Rosenberg, James N., 1926, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 885)
    - Rosenberg, Léonce, 1922-30 (Box 30, Folder 886)
    - Rosenborg, Ralph M., 1941-50 (Box 30, Folder 887)
    - Ross, Ralph P., 1933 (Box 30, Folder 888)
    - Ross, Robert Baldwin, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 889)
    - Rubinstein, Helena, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 890)
    - "S" general, 1912-50, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 891-894)
    - Saarinen, Aline B., 1950 (Box 31, Folder 895)
    - Sachs, Maurice, 1931 Feb 19 (Box 31, Folder 896)
    - Saga, Pietro de
      See: Steffi Kiesler, box 20, folders 577-579
    - St. Denis, Ruth, 1929, 1932 (Box 31, Folder 897)
    - St. Faith's House (Tarrytown, N.Y.), 1917-18 (Box 31, Folder 898)
    - Saint Paul's School (Garden City, N.Y.), 1950 Oct 10 (Box 31, Folder 899)
      See also: Mary F. Youngs, box 40, folder 1151
    - St. Stephen's College (Annandale-on- Hudson, N.Y.), 1928, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 900)
      See also: Bard College, box 4, folder 101
    - Salon des Réalités Nouvelles, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 901)
    - Salpeter, Harry, 1941 Feb 5 (Box 31, Folder 902)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1922-37 (Box 31, Folder 903)
    - Sandberg, Willem Henry Jacob Henri Berend, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 904)
    - Sargent, John Singer, 1913, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 905)
    - Sartorio, Angiola, 1948-51 (Box 31, Folder 906)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 907)
    - Saturday Review, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 908)
    - Savadsky, Marie
      See: Maria Zavadsky, box 40, folder 1154
    - Savadsky, Vassily
      See: Vassily Zavadsky, box 40, folder 1155
    - Savery, Halley
      See: Henry Art Gallery, box 9, folder 487
      See: Western Association of Art Museum Directors, box 37, folder 1092
    - Sawyer, Charles H.
      See: Yale University School of the Fine Arts, box 40, folders 1145-1146
    - Schapiro, Louis, 1944-45 (Box 31, Folder 909)
    - Schapiro, Meyer, 1940, 1944 (Box 31, Folder 910)
    - Scheiber, Hugo, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 911)
    - Schenker & Co., 1923-27, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 912)
    - Scheyer, E. E., 1924, 1926, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 913)
    - Schiff, John D., 1941-50, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 914)
    - Schlemmer, Oskar, 1927, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 915)
    - Schmitt-Rost, Hans, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 916)
    - School of Meditation, 1920, 1924, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 917)
    - Schottlaender, Julius, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 918)
    - Schreiber, Carl F.
    - Schroeder, Theodore Albert, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 919)
    - Schütze, Martin (Mrs.), 1921 (Box 31, Folder 920)
    - Schwitters, Ernst, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 921)
    - Schwitters, Eve, 1948 May 30 (Box 31, Folder 922)
    - Schwitters, Helma, 1926-37 (Box 31, Folder 923-924)
      See also: Kurt Schwitters, box 31, folders 925-926
    - Schwitters, Kurt, 1925-47, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 925-926)
      See also: Gertrud Mehrgut, box 23, folder 687
      See also: Edith Thomas, box 34, folder 995
    - Scott, Foresman and Company, 1942 Apr 28 (Box 31, Folder 927)
    - Sears, Edith Howland, 1920-29, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 928)
    - Seattle Art Museum, 1936 Sep 8 (Box 31, Folder 929)
    - Seattle Fine Arts Society, 1927-28 (Box 31, Folder 930)
    - Seaver, Esther Isabel, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 931)
    - Secker, Hans Friedrich, 1924 Jul 17 (Box 31, Folder 932)
    - Selden, Elizabeth, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 933)
    - Seligmann, Kurt, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 934)
    - Servranckx, Victor, 1926-49, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 935)
    - Sesqui-Centennial International Exposition (1926: Philadelphia, Pa.), 1926-27 (Box 32, Folder 936-937)
      See also: Box 84, folders 2153-2154
    - Seuphor, Michel, 1932-51 (Box 32, Folder 938)
    - Seymour, Charles
      See: Yale University President's Office, box 40, folders 1142-1144
    - Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1949-50 (Box 32, Folder 939)
    - Seymour, Gladys, 1950, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 940)
    - Seymour, Betsey
    - Shankar, Uday, 1938, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 941)
      See also: Hartwell, Jobson, and Kibbee, box 17, folder 479
    - Shawn, Ted, 1923-51, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 942-949)
      See also: Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, box 19, folder 537
    - Sidès, Alfredo
      See: Galerie René Gimpel, box 14, folder 384
      See: Salon des Réalités Nouvelles, box 31, folder 901
    - Sizer, Caroline F., 1942, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 950)
    - Sizer, Theodore
    - Smith College. Dept. of Art, 1921-25 (Box 33, Folder 951)
    - Soby, James Thrall, 1941-51 (Box 33, Folder 952)
    - Society of Independent Artists (New York, N.Y.), 1917-41, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 953-954)
      See also: Box 62, folders 1683-1684
    - Society of the Four Arts (Palm Beach, Fla.), 1937 (Box 33, Folder 955)
    - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1939-49, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 956-957)
    - Solotaroff, M., 1925-26, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 958)
    - Soviet Russia Today, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 959)
    - Speranza, Gino, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 960)
    - Spiecker, Otto H., 1927 (Box 33, Folder 961)
    - Spiecker, Siegfried W.
    - Springfield City Library Association (Springfield, Mass.), 1938 Aug 4 (Box 33, Folder 962)
    - Springfield Museum of Fine Arts
      See: Museum of Fine Arts (Springfield, Mass.), box 25, folders 730-731
    - Spur, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 963)
    - Spurr, B. M., 1919-29, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 964)
    - Stanislawski, Ryszard, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 965)
    - Steinitz, Kate Traumann, 1922, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 966)
    - Stella, Joseph, 1920-46, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 967-968)
    - Stella, Helen
    - Stevens, Will Henry, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 969)
    - Stieglitz, Alfred, 1920-31, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 970-971)
    - Stokes, Helen Louisa Phelps, [1928 Jan?] (Box 33, Folder 972)
    - Storm Petersen, Robert, 1927 Mar 10 (Box 33, Folder 973)
    - Storrs, John Henry Bradley, 1921-49, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 974)
    - Strong, Edward K., 1934 (Box 33, Folder 975)
    - Stuckenberg, Fritz, 1920-27 (Box 33, Folder 976)
    - Sturm, 1920-27, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 977-979)
    - Sullivan, Cornelius J., 1926-29, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 980)
    - Sullivan, Mary, 1920-31, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 981)
    - Sun (Baltimore, Md.), 1939 (Box 34, Folder 982)
    - Sun Insurance Office, Ltd., 1928-30 (Box 34, Folder 983)
    - Sunwise Turn, Inc., 1918-23, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 984)
    - Survey, 1919-29 (Box 34, Folder 985)
    - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1934, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 986)
    - Sweeney, Laura
    - Szépmuvészeti Múzeum (Hungary), 1928 May 9 (Box 34, Folder 987)
    - "T", general (Box 34, Folder 988)
    - Tarbell, Ida M., 1931-38, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 989)
    - Tasch & Sherbin, 1933, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 990)
    - Tchelitchew, Pavel, 1941-51, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 991)
    - Terry, Walter, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 992)
    - Thayer, Mabel, 1928, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 993)
    - Theatre Arts Magazine
      See: Sheldon Cheney, box 8, folder 217
    - Theatre Guild, 1932 May 17 (Box 34, Folder 994)
    - Thomas, Edith, 1947-48 (Box 34, Folder 995)
    - Thompson, Juliet, 1939, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 996)
    - Tietze, Hans, 1927 Mar 23 (Box 34, Folder 997)
    - Tiffany and Company, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 998)
    - Toledo Museum of Art, 1926, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 999)
    - Toole & Cooper, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 1000)
    - Torres-García, Joaquín, 1921, 1929, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1001)
    - Tovell, Ruth Massey, 1929 Apr 21 (Box 34, Folder 1002)
    - Town Hall Club, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 1003)
    - Transatlantic Shipping Company, 1920-21 (Box 34, Folder 1004)
      See also: Oversize, box 118, folder 2796
    - Tremaine, Emily, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 1005)
    - Trexler, Charles, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 1006)
    - Trexler, Samuel Geiss, 1935-41, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1007)
    - Trudeau, E. L., n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1008)
    - Trust Company of North America, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1009)
      Includes receipts to Man Ray.
    - Tschichold, Jan, 1935 May 9 (Box 34, Folder 1010)
    - Tschudy, Herbert B., n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1011)
      See also: Brooklyn Museum, box 6, folders 152-157
      See also: Collectors of American Art, Inc., box 9, folder 241
    - Tugal, Pierre, 1937 Jul 16 (Box 34, Folder 1012)
    - Tukernborg, Johanne, 1923 Jan 11 (Box 34, Folder 1013)
      Contains 7 prints.
    - Tuskegee Institute, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 1014)
    - Tworkov, Jack, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1015)
    - "U", general (Box 34, Folder 1016)
    - Uhde, Wilhelm, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1017)
    - Underwood, Oscar Wilder (Box 34, Folder 1018)
    - Unitarian Service Committee, Inc., 1948-49 (Box 34, Folder 1019)
    - United Neighborhood Houses of New York, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1020)
    - United States. Bureau of Education, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1021)
    - Unity School of Christianity, 1932 Feb 12 (Box 34, Folder 1022)
    - University Film Foundation, 1930-31 (Box 34, Folder 1023)
    - University of Chicago. Renaissance Society, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 1024)
    - University of Minnesota. University Gallery, 1937, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1025)
    - University of Pennsylvania. University Museum, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1026)